Too Mean to Forgive... Too Mad to Forget!
The Last Hard Men is a western film directed by Andrew V. McLaglen.
In 1909 Arizona, retired lawman Sam Burgade's life is thrown upside-down when his old enemy Provo and six
other convicts escape a chain-gang in the Yuma Territorial Prison and come gunning for Burgade.
Sam Burgade, played by Charlton Heston.
Provo, played by James Coburn.
Susan Burgade, played by Barbara Hershey.
Menendez, played by Jorge Rivero.
Noel Nye, played by Michael Parks.
Shelby, played by Larry Wilcox.
The Last Hard Men is a 1976 American Western film directed by Andrew
McLaglen, based on the 1969 novel Gundown by Brian Garfield.
It stars Charlton Heston and James Coburn, with supporting roles by Barbara Hershey,
Jorge Rivero, Michael Parks, and Larry Wilcox in his screen debut.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
fugitive, on the run, gunfight, arizona territory.